dwellstudio.com 2012-05-28

# Privacy Policy by DwellStudio

By sharing our Privacy Policy, we hope to reassure you that by joining the DwellStudio family, we are equally appreciative of your business and respectful of your requests to protect your personal information. When you purchase or order a product from DwellStudio, or register on our website to receive a catalog, you may choose to give us basic information such as your name, email address, mailing/billing address, zip code, phone and credit card information. When you visit our Web site, we may collect more information such as your Internet service provider's address, the name of the Web page directing you, as well as your activity while on our site. This tracking helps us understand how to better service our customers. The information that you give us, and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with other select companies whose products you may find useful. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with other companies, please email us at [unsubscribe@dwellstudio.com.](mailto:%20unsubscribe@dwellstudio.com)

## User Comments and Reviews

We welcome your input and feedback on our products and designs. Please note that any comments, reviews, notes, messages or ideas sent to our website or customer service (collectively "Comments") shall be and remain the exclusive property of DwellStudio. Your submission of any Comments shall constitute an assignment to DwellStudio of all worldwide rights, titles and interest in all copyrights and other intellectual property rights in the Comments.

## Links to other Web Sites

Our Web Site may contain helpful links or hyperlinks to our brand partners and other outside services and resources maintained by third parties. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy and we recommend reviewing these privacy policies before disclosing any personal information on any other sites.

## Update Your Information

Updating your contact and mailing information so that you can receive the latest news, catalogues and promotions from DwellStudio is easy. Just contact customerservice@dwellstudio.com and provide your previous and current full name, mailing address, email address and phone number.

## Security Policy

The security of your information is very important to us. We use 256-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. SSL technology encrypts your order information to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than DwellStudio.

Once you enter the checkout page your computer will begin communicating with our server in secure mode. When you enter a secure portion of a website, an image of a closed lock or a solid key will appear in your browser window. If you click on this image, a small pop-up window displaying website security information will appear. This display indicates that your personal information is transmitted in encrypted form to a DwellStudio web server, not to some unknown or unauthorized server.

While we implement these and other security measures on our sites, please note that 100% security is not always possible. You play a role in protecting your information as well. Because your password permits access to your personal information, please keep your password secret and do not disclose it to others.
